<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DesiiApp</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="fb_banner_placement">2932553903737866_2937463686580221</string>
    <string name="fb_interstetial_placement">2932553903737866_2938000299859893</string>
    <string name="fb_medium_placement">2932553903737866_2938016183191638</string>
    <string name="fb_native_placement">2932553903737866_2938669599792963</string>
    <string name="sponsored">Sponsored</string>


    <!--<string name="admob_app_id">ca-app-pub-3514531051471948~7018478881</string>-->
    <string name="admob_app_id">ca-app-pub-4893014899282887~3283790575</string>
    <!-- <string name="admob_app_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544~3347511713</string>-->
    <string name="banner_home_footer">ca-app-pub-3514531051471948/4200743854</string>
    <string name="rewarded_video">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/5224354917</string>
    <string name="add_open">ca-app-pub-4893014899282887/2892778457</string>
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3514531051471948/4200743854</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="term">We requests you to carefully go through these Terms @amp; Conditions (“ Terms of Service ” or “Agreement” or “ToS ”) and our Community Guidelines prior to using or availing access to the Application. If You continue to browse and use this Application, You irrevocably and unconditionally are agreeing to comply with, abide by and be bound by all the obligations as stipulated in this ToS, which together read with our Privacy Policy and any other applicable policies referred to herein or made available on the Application, shall govern the Company’s relationship with You in relation to the Application. These ToS only apply to the Application, or to any such platform wherein you are allowed to access the Services of the Application, and not to any other application, web site or any offline activities by the Company (unless expressly and specifically stated).\nThese ToS supersede all previous oral and written terms and conditions (if any) communicated to You and shall act as a binding Agreement between Company and the Users (as defined hereunder).\nIF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY ALL CONDITIONS/CLAUSES CAPTURED IN THIS TOS, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE APPLICATION OR SERVICES.</string>
    <string name="term1">1. Definitions\nApp or “Application” shall mean and include the software and mobile Application accessed through or downloaded from the App store i.e. Android or IOS, and accessible from any platforms where the Application functions such as mobile phones, tablets and any such other devices. For the purpose of this ToS, the Application shall mean DesiiApp, and any improvement or modifications to the same as released by the Company later.\nContent means and includes, without limitation, any information, data, text, audio, video, gifs, polls, User profiles, software, tags, graphics, and interactive features generated, provided, or otherwise made accessible either by you or by us or our partners or Sponsors on or through the Service.\nService(s) means services provided through the App, as described in further detail under clause 3 below. The Services provided through the Application may change from time to time, at the sole discretion of the Company.\n“You” or “User” or “Consumer” shall mean any registered user of the Application, or his/her representatives or affiliates who are registered on the Application.\n
“DesiiAppp” shall mean any post by a registered user on the Application.
</string>
    <string name="term2">2. Updation of Terms\nYour use of the Applications is subject to these ToS, which may be updated, amended, modified or
     revised by us from time to time without notice to You. It is important for You to refer to these
     ToS from time to time to make sure that You are aware of any additions, revisions, amendments or
     modifications that we may have made to these ToS.
</string>
    <string name="term3">3. Service(s) provided to Users\nThe Application provides You with the ability to (all together the “Services”):\n
     I. Create and maintain your own profile on the Application after registration (described in
     clause 4 below);\n
     II. Choose and implement privacy settings on your account. This gives you the ability to
     determine which other Users can view your profile and/or any other Content uploaded by you on
     the Application. This includes the ability to specifically block certain other Users of the
     Application from accessing your account;\n
     III. Post your thoughts, opinions and updates on the application\n
     IV. Follow other users on the application\n
     V. React (Like, Dislike, Comment, Share) to other users\n
     VI. You may remove any of your uploaded Koos, comments\n
     VII. Block other users\n
     VIII. You may use hashtags to highlight the topic on which you are posting\n
     IX. The Company may also, at any time and its own discretion, remove any posts that are found to
     be in breach of any of the terms and conditions contained in this ToS or any other
     policies/documents prepared in this regard by the Company;\n
     X. Users can hold one-to-one chats with other Users on the Application, provided they have not
     been blocked/restricted by such Users.

     The Company reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify or replace all or any part of
     the ToS, or change, suspend, or discontinue all or any part of the Services at any time by
     posting a notice on the Service or by sending You an email. Your continued use of the Service
     following the posting of any changes to the ToS constitutes acceptance of those changes. Any
     information You provide to us for the purposes of registering and setting up your account shall
     be considered as accurate, complete and updated. You are solely responsible for the activity
     that occurs on Your account and for maintaining the security of the Application and any
     information You input to the Application. Further, we are not responsible for the accuracy or
     legitimacy of any data, information or Content uploaded or posted by you on the Application
     during your usage of the Services. Similarly, we are not responsible for any information and/or
     Content uploaded, displayed, created or posted on the Application by other Users. Any reliance
     by you on any information or Content provided by any other User will be your responsibility. You
     understand and agree that the Company will not be liable for any damages, losses, harm or costs
     incurred by you as a result of your reliance on any information provided by any other User. You
     shall not use or access another User’s account without such other User’s explicit permission.
     You will immediately notify us in writing of any unauthorized use of Your account, or any other
     account-related security breach of which You are aware. You can access the Application through
     your account maintained in the Application. The details regarding registration and creation of
     an account are captured in clause 4 below. The account is provided on a best-efforts as-is
     basis. While we strive to maintain the highest levels of service availability, we will not be
     liable for any interruption that may be caused to Your access of the Services.\n
</string>

    <string name="term4">4. Registration and Account Integrity\nWhen you download the Application, you will first be asked to choose the language you would like
     to use the Application in (this preference can be changed in the settings page of the
     Application at any time). On accepting the ToS and PP after this, you will automatically be
     redirected to the account creation and registration process. As part of the registration
     process/for creating your account, you will need to provide us with your phone number or email
     address, (which will be verified via a one-time password).

     It is Your responsibility to ensure that the information You provide is accurate, secure, and
     not misleading. You can then create an account username/handle and password for yourself. You
     cannot create an account username and/or password using\n
     (i) the names and information of another person; or\n
     (ii) using words that are the trademarks or the property of another party (including ours); or\n
     (iii) words that are vulgar, obscene or in any other way inappropriate.\n

     Please note that If a username has been used by a verified user on another platform, in order to
     avoid risk of impersonation, the username will not be allotted to anyone else and, if already
     allotted, may be cancelled at the discretion of posts without any notice.

     We reserve the right with or without notice to suspend or terminate any account in breach of the
     above conditions. On the creation of your account, you can modify your handle/username at any
     time. You may also add a description of yourself to your account. If for any reason you suspect
     that your username and password has been disclosed to or obtained by another party, you should
     contact us immediately. Please note that we never contact Users requesting them to confirm their
     username, password or any other details, except when the User is signing into the Application.\n
</string>
    <string name="term5"> 5. Fees and Payment\nThere is no fee and/or payment required to be made by you prior to, during, or after your usage
     of the Application. The usage of the Application is completely free of cost, and any request for
     fees or payment by any person/entity purporting to be a representative of the Company should be
     ignored by you, unless the same is reflected in an updated version of these ToS.
</string>
    <string name="term6"> 6. Use of Your Information and Content\nIf You create, transmit, submit, display or otherwise make available any information and Content
     while using the Service, You may provide only information that You own or have the right to use.
     Although you remain the sole and complete owner of all information and Content provided and / or
     uploaded by you on the Application (including any intellectual property rights in the same), you
     give us a license to fully use that information in connection with providing you the Services to
     the best of our abilities. This includes a perpetual, royalty-free and worldwide license to use
     any of the content created by you for advertising and marketing purposes, in order to promote
     the Application among third-parties. However, we may only use the information You provide as
     permitted by our Privacy Policy, and applicable law. For example, we will never share Your
     personally identifiable information without Your prior permission.

     Please closely review our Privacy Policy for more information regarding how we use and disclose
     Your personal information. Our Privacy Policy is hereby incorporated into these Terms of Use by
     this reference.

     We reserve the right to maintain, delete or destroy all information, Content and materials
     posted or uploaded through the Service(s) pursuant to our internal record retention and/or
     destruction policies, upon reasonable notice provided to the you. We (may / may not) make use of
     third party cloud services provider or our own service infrastructure for hosting the servers
     and databases. While we make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that the data stored on
     our servers is persistent and always available to the User, we will not be responsible in the
     event of failure of the third-party servers or any other factors outside our reasonable control,
     that may cause the User data to be permanently deleted, irretrievable, or temporarily
     inaccessible.
     You hereby agree and acknowledge that the Company reserves the right to disable, destroy or
     delete any Content uploaded by You on the Application, if such Content is found to be duplicated
     and/or replicated on any other media apart from the Application. You further agree and
     acknowledge that the Company also reserves the right to remove or refuse to publish Your
     Content, in whole or part, at any time, at the Companys sole discretion, with or without notice
     to You
</string>

    <string name="term7"> 7. Third Party Services\nThe Company may provide Users with links to, or contact information for, third party sites or
     services. The Company is not responsible for, and does not endorse, any third-party content,
     sites, or services mentioned on the Service. It is hereby stated that Company shall in no way be
     responsible for any acts or omissions of third parties whom the User may connect with through a
     mechanism facilitated by Company. Any transaction, dealings or communication otherwise that the
     User may have with such third parties are at the User’s own risk and we make no warranties,
     express or implied regarding the quality or suitability of the services or products of such
     third-party vendors.
</string>
    <string name="term8">8. Rules and Conduct\nAdditionally, You shall not host, display, upload, modify, publish, transmit, update or share
     any information that:\n
     (i) may be harmful to minors or children below the age of 18 (eighteen) years;\n
     (ii) threatens the unity, integrity, defence, security or sovereignty of India, friendly
     relations with foreign states or public order or causes incitement to the commission of any
     cognisable offence or prevents investigation of any offence or is insulting any other nation;
     and\n
     (iii) is invasive of another privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically objectionable,
     disparaging, relating or encouraging money laundering or gambling, or otherwise unlawful in any
     manner whatever\n
     (iv) grossly harmful\n
     (v) pornographic\n
     (vi) paedophilic\n
</string>
    <string name="term9"> 9. Alerts Provided by The Company\nThe Application provides you with multiple automatic alerts, if\n
     (a) another User likes a content posted by you; or\n
     (b) another User follows you; or\n
     (c) any other similar relevant. You can opt-in or opt-out of such alerts in the settings section
     of the app.\n
     You understand and agree that any alerts provided to you through the Service may be delayed or
     prevented by a variety of factors. We will do our best to provide alerts in a timely manner with
     accurate information. However, we neither guarantee the delivery nor the accuracy of the content
     of any alert. You also agree that we shall not be liable for any delays, failure to deliver, or
     misdirected delivery of any alert; for any errors in the content of an alert; or for any actions
     taken or not taken by You or any third party in reliance on an alert.
</string>
    <string name="term10"> 10. Content Ownership and Copyright Conditions of Access\nThe Content listed on the Application are either\n
     (i) User generated, or\n
     (ii) belong to Company.\n

     The nature of ownership and use of the information and Content uploaded and/or provided by you
     has been clarified in clause 6 above. Your copying of the copyrighted content published by
     Company on the Application for any commercial purpose or for the purpose of earning profit will
     be a violation of copyright and Company reserves its rights under applicable law accordingly.

     We authorize the User to view and access the content available on or from the Application solely
     for receiving, interacting, delivering and communicating only as per this Agreement. The
     contents of the Application, information, text, graphics, images, logos, button icons, software
     code, design, and the collection, arrangement and assembly of content on the Application
     (collectively, "Our Content"), are our property and are protected under copyright, trademark and
     other laws. User shall not modify Our Content or reproduce, display, publicly perform,
     distribute, or otherwise use Our Content in any way for any public or commercial purpose or for
     personal gain.

     Users are prohibited from accessing the Services for purposes of monitoring their availability,
     performance or functionality, or for any other benchmarking or competitive purposes.
</string>
    <string name="term11"> 11. Reviews and Feedback\nYou are solely responsible for the Content that You choose to submit for publication on the
     Application, including any feedback, ratings, or reviews (“Critical Content”) relating to the
     Application or other Users. Our role in publishing the Critical Content is restricted to that of
     an ‘intermediary’ under the Information Technology Act, 2000. We disclaim all responsibility
     with respect to the content of Critical Content, and our role with respect to such content is
     restricted to our obligations as an ‘intermediary’ under the said Act. We shall not be liable to
     pay any consideration to any User for re-publishing any content across any of our platforms.
     You agree that we may contact You through telephone, email, SMS, or any other electronic means
     of communication for the purpose of:\n
     I. Obtaining feedback in relation to Application or our Services; and/or\n
     II. Obtaining feedback in relation to any other Users listed on the Application; and/or\n
     III. Resolving any complaints, information, or queries by other Users regarding Your Critical
     Content;\n
     and you agree to provide your fullest co-operation further to such communication by Company.
</string>

    <string name="term12"> 12. Profile Ownership and Editing Rights\nWe ensure easy access to the Users by providing a tool to update Your profile information. We
     reserve the right to moderate the changes or updates requested by You, and we shall take the
     independent decision whether to publish or reject the requests submitted for the respective
     changes or updates in Your profile. You hereby represent and warrant that You are fully entitled
     under law to upload all Content uploaded by You as part of Your profile or otherwise while using
     our Services, and that no such content breaches any third-party rights, including intellectual
     property rights. Upon becoming aware of a breach of the foregoing representation, we may modify
     or delete parts of Your profile information at our sole discretion with or without notice to
     You.
</string>

    <string name="term13"> 13. Rights and Obligation relating to the Content\nUsers shall be prohibited from:
     I. violating or attempting to violate the integrity or security of the Application or any
     content thereof;\n
     II. transmitting any information (including job posts, messages and hyperlinks) on or through
     the Application that is disruptive or competitive to the provision of our Services;\n
     III. intentionally submitting on the Application any incomplete, false or inaccurate
     information;\n
     IV. making any unsolicited communications to other Users;\n
     V. using any engine, software, tool, agent or other device or mechanism (such as spiders,
     robots, avatars or intelligent agents) to navigate or search the Application;\n
     VI. attempting to decipher, decompile, disassemble or reverse engineer any part of the
     Application;\n
     VII. copying or duplicating in any manner any of our Content or other information available from
     the Application;\n
     VIII. framing or hot linking or deep linking any Content.\n
     IX. circumventing or disabling any digital rights management, usage rules, or other security
     features of the Application.\n
     X. using the Platform or App manner that is unethical or illegal or disruptive.\n

     The Company shall, upon obtaining knowledge by itself or been brought to actual knowledge by an
     affected person in writing or through email signed with electronic signature about any such
     information as mentioned above, be entitled to disable such information that is in contravention
     of this Clause. We shall also be entitled to preserve such information and associated records
     for at least 120 (one hundred twenty) days for production to governmental authorities for
     investigation purposes.\n\n

     In case of non-compliance with any applicable laws, rules or regulations, or the Agreement
     (including the Privacy Policy) by a User, we shall have the right to immediately terminate Your
     access or usage rights to the Application and Services and to remove non-compliant information
     from the Application.
</string>
    <string name="privacy_value">THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT

The following lists the information we collect from you and how we use it:
Information We Collect: \n\n\n

(a) Log-in Data:   User ID, mobile phone number, email ID, gender (optional), and IP address. We may collect an indicative age range which tells us that you are of the appropriate age to access our Platform and certain features of our Platform (collectively “Log-in Data”).

Content You Share:  This comprises of all the information you make available to other users via the Platform, such as:

·   Information about you or relating to you that is voluntarily shared by you on the Platform, including without limitation, any quotes, images, political opinions, religious views, profile photo, user bio and handle, inter alia.

·   Any posts that you make on the Platform.

Information we receive from other sources: . We may also be working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, analytics providers, search information providers) and may receive information about you from such sources. Such data may be shared internally and combined with the data collected on this Platform. \n\n\n

(b) Log Data: "Log Data" is information that we automatically collect when you use the Platform, whether through the use of cookies, web beacons, log files, scripts, including, but not limited to:

· technical information, such as your mobile carrier-related information, configuration information made available by your web browser or other programs you use to access the Platform, your IP address and your device’s version and identification number;

· information about what you have searched for and viewed while using the Platform, such as web search terms used, social media profiles visited, mini applications used, and details of other information and content accessed or requested by you while using the Platform;

· general information about communications on the platform, such as the identity of a user that you have communicated with and the time, data and duration of your communications; and

· metadata, which means information related to items you have made available through the Platform, such as the date, time or location that a shared photograph or video was taken or posted. \n\n\n

(c) Cookies: Our Platform uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our Platform. This helps us to provide you with a good user experience when you browse our Platform and allows us to improve the Platform. We collect the cookie data from the cookies on your device. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them, kindly see our cookie policy \n\n\n

(d) Surveys: If you choose to participate in a survey, we may request you to provide certain Personal Information i.e. any information that could be used to identify you (“Personal Information”). We may use a third-party service provider to conduct these surveys and this will be notified to you prior to the completion of the survey.\n\n\n

(e) User Search Data:   Any searches that are conducted by you on the Platform.\n\n\n

(f) Additional Account Security: We collect your phone number and request access to the SMSes on your phone by sending you a One-Time-Password (“OTP”), which you confirm by entering the OTP to verify your identity, while registering with our Platform.\n\n\n

(g) Contacts List: We access the contacts list on your mobile device. We always ask for your consent before accessing your contacts list and you have the option to deny us the access to your contacts list.\n\n\n

(h) Location Information: "Location Data" is information that is derived from your GPS, IP address, and/or public posts that contain location information.\n\n\n

You will disclose certain location information to us and to other Platform users when you access the Platform, as we derive location information from your IP address, device, or internet service for providing the Services or improving our platform such as to ensure that there are no multiple log-ins on your account.\n\n\n

(i) Customer Support Information: Any information that you provide to our customer support team regarding any assistance or support that you may require for using our Platform from time to time.\n\n\n

(j) Device Data: “Device Data” includes without limitation, the following:\n\n\n

§    Device attributes: information such as the operating system, operating system version and language, hardware and software versions, device company and model, screen resolution, battery level, signal strength, device RAM, device bitrate, available storage space, information pertaining to the device CPU, browser type, app and file names and types, and plugins.\n

§    Device operations: information about operations and behaviours performed on the device, such as whether a window is foregrounded or backgrounded.\n

§    Identifiers: unique identifiers, device IDs, ad IDs, and other identifiers, such as from games, apps or accounts you use.\n

§    Device signals:  we may collect your Bluetooth signals, and information about nearby Wi-Fi access points, beacons, and cell towers.\n

§    Data from device settings: information you allow us to receive through device settings you turn on, such as access to your GPS location, camera or photos.\n

§   Network and connections: information such as the name of your mobile operator or ISP, network type and speed, data consumption, language, time zone, mobile phone number, IP address and connection speed.\n

§    Application and application version: any mobile applications that are stored on your mobile device.\n

§    Media: we access the media gallery on your mobile device, including without limitation, images, videos and audio files and the storage space on your phone. However, we shall always obtain your consent before accessing your images and you shall have the option to deny us such access.\n


How We Use It\n\n\n


· To set up and facilitate log-in to a user account on Platform;\n

· To notify you about changes to the Platform, including this Privacy Policy;\n

· To facilitate communication, including provision of user support;\n

· To enforce our terms, conditions, and policies and any of our rights, or the rights of our affiliate companies, or other users of the Platform;\n

· To develop new services and improve the existing services and the Platform and integrate user feedback and requests;\n

· To provide language and location based personalization;\n

· To administer the Platform and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, security, fraud-detection, account management, and survey purposes;\n

· To better understand how you use and access the Platform and to improve the user experience on the Platform;\n

· To pseudonymise and aggregate your information, including Personal Information, for conducting user demographic analysis on items such as region, phone model, operating system platform, system language, and the Platform version in order to better understand how our users are using the Platform;\n

· To pseudonymise and aggregate your information, including Personal Information, for collection of web and account traffic statistics of what content and services are used when users access third-party services on the Platform;\n

· To upload or create replicable profiles on associated/ sister platforms;\n

·To assess effectiveness of and improve advertising and other marketing and promotional activities\n

To provide you quick access to your previous searches. To use analytics for personalization and to show you targeted advertisements.\n

To verify your identity and for maintaining your account security. We request access to your SMS folder to automatically read the OTP generated.\n

To provide suggestions and invite your friends and other contacts to the platform and to notify you when any individual joins the platform.\n

· For security, fraud-detection and account management;\n

· To be used for enhanced content targeting;\n

· To provide you with location-based services that you choose to use:\n

§  mini applications that may be made available on the Platform from time to time, which may require such information based on the services that they provide (if you choose to disclose your location to any mini application);\n

§  To provide language and location customisation.\n

To help provide you support and assistance\n

· To facilitate the sharing of any videos and images using the Platform;\n

· To customise our Platform to suit your mobile device;\n

· For purposes of camera configurations;\n

· Understand whether there is enough storage space on your device to be able to download any content from the Platform for the purposes of sharing via WhatsApp and/or Facebook;\n

· To optimise your user experience on our Platform;\n

· To deliver optimal user video experience;\n

· To verify your identity so as to enforce our terms, conditions, and policies;\n

· To improve the Platform.\n

·To be used for purposes of location feed\n

· To derive user language/personalisation;\n

· To facilitate the sharing of any content on the Platform via the applications downloaded on your mobile device;\n

· To improve the quality of camera lenses\n

DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION\n


We disclose your information in the following manner:

Content Visible to Others

Public Content i.e., any content you post on your user profile or on another user’s profile, such as a post comment is accessible to everyone, including search engines. Any information you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Platform, including your profile page information, is accessible to anyone. When you submit, post or share the content that you choose to make public on the Platform, it may be re-shared by others. You should consider who you choose to share it with, because people who can see your activity on our Platform can choose to share it with others on and off our Platform, including people outside the audience you shared it with.

Users can also use our Platform to create and share content about you with the audience that they choose, such as posting a photo of you or tagging you in any of their posts. We reserve the right to share all public content on any social media site or any other online or offline platform. We will never rent or sell your Personal Information to third parties, except on an anonymized basis, unless expressly provided in this Privacy Policy.

Sharing with our Group of Companies

We may share your Personal Information with any member of our Group. The term “Group” shall mean any entity that is controlled by us, or any entity that is in control of us, or any entity that is under common control with us, whether directly or indirectly.

What you Share with Others

When you share content and communicate using our Platform, you choose the audience who can view such content. For example, when you post any content from our Platform on Facebook, you select the audience for the post, such as a friend, a group of friends or all of your friends. Similarly, when you use WhatsApp or any other application on your mobile device to share the content on our Platform, you choose who you share the content with. We do not control and shall not be liable for the manner, in which such persons (with whom you choose to share content via any sharing options, such as WhatsApp or Facebook, available on the Platform) use the information that you share with them.

Sharing with Third Parties

We may share your information (including Personal Information) with select third parties including:

- Business partners, suppliers and subcontractors (“Affiliates”). Affiliates may use this information to help provide, understand, and improve the Service and Affiliates’ own services for the performance of any contract that we enter into with you.\n

- Advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others. We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that any given number of women in a specified age group clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target.\n

- Government bodies or law enforcement agencies, if we have good-faith belief that it is reasonably necessary to share your personal data or information in order to comply with any legal obligation or any government request; or to protect the rights or prevent any harm to the property, or safety of the Company, our customers, or public; or to detect, prevent or otherwise address public safety, fraud, security or technical issues.\n

We may also disclose your information (including Personal Information) to select third parties in the following circumstances:\n

- If the Company or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets. If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, reorganization, or sale of assets such that your information would be transferred or become subject to a different Privacy Policy, we will notify you in advance so you can opt out of any such new policy by deleting your account before transfer.\n

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY\n\n

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you (for example, by email or a sign-in notification or some other means). We will obtain your consent for all the material changes to this Privacy Policy.</string>


</resources>